<resources>
    <string name="google_ads_id">ca-app-pub-9857474328493181~6435138107</string>
    <string name="interstitial_ads_id">ca-app-pub-9857474328493181/2304321402</string>
    <string name="app_name">Shobiz TV</string>
    <string name="shzbiz_icon_description">SHZBiz Icon</string>
    <string name="homepage">Homepage</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy_description">Learn more about ShoBiz Android Live TV privacy policy</string>
    <string name="system_update">System Update</string>
    <string name="system_update_description">Check system update for latest updates.</string>
    <string name="help_and_feedback">Help and feedback</string>
    <string name="help_and_feedback_description">Contact us when you are facing issues on our app</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_description">Learn more about ShoBiz TV Android Live.</string>
    <string name="videos_and_more"><![CDATA[Videos & more]]></string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="version">Version</string>
    <string name="about_image_description">About image desc</string>
    <string name="about_details">Shobiz Android TV app is designed to bring continuous live TV streaming and a wide array of entertainment programs directly to your Android TV or smart TV. With its 24/7 live TV feature, users can enjoy real-time streaming of their favorite channels, ensuring they never miss a moment of their preferred shows or events.\n\nShobiz provides an extensive library of entertainment programs, offering unlimited access to movies, series, documentaries, and more. Users can explore a diverse range of content, catering to various tastes and preferences.\n</string>
    <string name="help_and_feedback_details">Shobiz Android TV app is designed to bring continuous live TV streaming and a wide array of entertainment programs directly to your Android TV or smart TV. With its 24/7 live TV feature, users can enjoy real-time streaming of their favorite channels, ensuring they never miss a moment of their preferred shows or events.\n\nShobiz provides an extensive library of entertainment programs, offering unlimited access to movies, series, documentaries, and more. Users can explore a diverse range of content, catering to various tastes and preferences.\n</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_details">Effective Date: [Insert Effective Date]\n\nThis Privacy Policy describes how SHOBIZ TV (\"we,\" \"us,\" or \"our\") collects, uses, shares, and protects the personal information of users (“you” or “users”) who interact with the Shobiz Android TV App (\"App\").\n\n1. Information We Collect\n1.1. Information You Provide: When you use our App, we may collect information that you voluntarily provide, such as:\n • Account registration information (name, email address, etc.).\n • Payment information (if applicable).\n • User-generated content (comments, ratings, etc.).\n\n1.2. Automatically Collected Information: We may automatically collect certain information when you use the App, including:\n • Device information (device type, operating system version, etc.).\n • Usage data (pages visited, features used, etc.).\n • Log data and analytics.\n\n2. How We Use Your Information\nWe may use the collected information for the following purposes:\n • To provide and personalize the App’s features and content.\n • To process transactions and fulfill user requests.\n • To improve the App’s functionality and user experience.\n • To communicate with users regarding updates, promotions, and important information.\n • To analyze usage patterns and trends.\n\n3. Information Sharing and Disclosure\nWe may share your information in the following circumstances:\n • With service providers who assist us in providing the App’s features.\n • In response to legal requests or to protect our rights.\n • With your consent or as otherwise disclosed at the time of data collection.\n\n4. Data Security\nWe take reasonable measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.\n\n5. Third-Party Links and Services\nThe App may contain links to third-party websites or services not operated by us. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties.\n\n6. Children’s Privacy\nThe App is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children.\n\n7. Your Choices\nYou can manage your information by accessing your account settings or contacting us.\n\n8. Updates to This Policy\nWe may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify users of any material changes.\n\n9. Contact Us\nIf you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@shobiztv.com.</string>
    <string name="back4app_app_id">LFxdrkiHth3flbAcOu6O9Vi0B355pLt0n3JS3eSG</string>
    <string name="back4app_client_key">250Ri8dpCFkVa98s4afFgXZnk0qaE15pNoFzws1H</string>
    <string name="back4app_server_url">https://parseapi.back4app.com/</string>
    <string name="error_message">Please check your internet connection and also make sure that date and time is correct .</string>
</resources>